Class of 1944 Records, 1940-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1944 Records
1940-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1944.
RG 80 UUID:4674f605-20b4-4a84-83da-54aa66d9b0ef
12 boxes (5.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1944.
The Class of 1944 was the sixty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1944 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1944, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1944 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Sunday 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Photographs 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Speaker 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1940-1941 (Box 2142, Folder 5)
- Groups 1940-1944 (Box 2142, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1966-1975, 2004 (Box 2142, Folder 9)
- Officers 1943 (Box 2142, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 2142, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 2142, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 2142, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 2142, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2142, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 2142, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2142, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 2142, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 2142, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2142, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2142, Folder 21)
- Reunions undated (Box 2142, Folder 22)
- Reunion Newsletter 1994-2002 (Box 2142, Folder 23)
- Senior Day 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 24)
- Songs 1940-1944 (Box 2142, Folder 25)
- Sophomore Carnival 1942 (Box 2142, Folder 26)
- Sophomore Push 1942 (Box 2142, Folder 27)
- Class Supper 1944 (Box 2142, Folder 28)